{"data":[{"question":"There are 112 pounds in _______.","a":"one hundredweight","b":"two hundredweights","c":"four hundredweight","d":"eight hundredweights","answer":"1","explain":"\n - Hundredweight: unit of weight equal to 100 pounds ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"This case is too _______ for your grandmother to carry.","a":"heavy","b":"weight","c":"weigh","d":"much heavy","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Too + ajd + for somebody to do some thing ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My wife is very worried about gaining _______.","a":"weigh","b":"weighs","c":"weighed","d":"weight","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Gain weight: increase weight ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Two pints of beer make a little more than _______.","a":"half a litre","b":"a litre","c":"a quarter of a litre","d":"four litres","answer":"2","explain":"\n-1 US pint = 473.176473 milliliters ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"One hundredweight has ______ kilograms.","a":"100","b":"112","c":"50.8","d":"18","answer":"3","explain":"\n- One hundredweight: a unit of weight equal to 112 pounds \n- 1 pound = 453.59237 grams ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Two hundredweight are ________ kilos.","a":"202","b":"52","c":"101","d":"404","answer":"3","explain":"\n- One hundredweight: a unit of weight equal to 112 pounds \n- 1 pound = 453.59237 grams ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I _______12 stone.","a":"am","b":"weigh","c":"have","d":"weight","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Give me a ________ packet of chocolates, please.","a":"six-ounce","b":"six ounce","c":"six ounces","d":"six-ounces","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"This sack of potatoes weighs ________.","a":"one hundredweight","b":"ten hundredweights","c":"ten hundredweight","d":"twenty hundredweight","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A sack is a bag, especially a large one for carrying or storing goods, often contains 50 kg","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"This is too ______ for the little girl to carry.","a":"weight","b":"heavy","c":"much heavy","d":"weigh","answer":"2","explain":"- Too adjective to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}